虚幻勇士冒险 S2E7 XANA崛起第二部分 由özberk özen制作
视频来源：https://youtu.be/9KzGvCbcj84 中文字幕由熙洛Chincode制作 翻译：Albeta 校对：jky
Hey, Aelita, where's Einstein?
嘿 Aelita 我们的爱因斯坦在哪里？
Jeremy's working with my father at the factory.
Jeremy在工厂里和我父亲一起工作
A new program, about what?
研发新程序吗 关于什么的新程序？
This new program that'll make us stronger in the real world.
这个新程序会让我们在现实世界中更加强大
Oh, more power! I love it!
哦 变得更强大啊 我喜欢
New powers for Odd? He will brag even more.
Odd的新力量？他又会到处吹嘘了
I will never brag.
我才不会吹嘘
Don't make me laugh, Odd. Everyone knows you love to brag!
别逗我笑了 Odd 每个人都知道你喜欢吹牛!
Think whatever you want my buddy. I can't change your mind!
随你怎么想 兄弟 我没法改变你的想法!
Actually, I'm not bragging because I'm saying the truth.
实际上 我不是在吹牛 因为我说的就是事实
The truth? Are you really saying the truth?
真的？你真的在说实话吗？
Yes
是的
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈!
I will never forget the Sissi's reaction when she saw you.
我永远不会忘记茜茜看到你时的反应
WHAT?!
什么？
Ulrich!
You're right, Odd. It was awesome!
好吧 Odd 这真是太棒了
I don't know what we would do without return to the past.
我不知道如果没有时间倒转系统 我们要怎么办
Very true, return to the past saved our lives so many times.
非常正确 时间倒转系统救了我们很多次
I don't want to die because of XANA, so thank you Franz Hopper!
我可不想因为XANA而死 所以多谢Franz Hopper!
Let's say that Franz Hopper saved your butt a lot of times.
要我来说 应该是Franz Hopper救了你很多次
Yes, we can say that. This time I agree with you.
好吧 我们可以这样说 这一次我同意你的说法
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈!
What should we do now?
我们现在应该做什么？
Don't forget Odd, we have class with Ms. Hertz.
别忘了Odd 我们有Hertz老师的课
How could you forget, Odd? Your favorite class after all.
你怎么能忘记呢 Odd？毕竟是你最喜欢的课
I never liked that lesson.
我从来不喜欢那门课
But you never notice because you always sleep in the class.
不过你从不注意 因为你总是在课堂上睡觉
Let's go, before it's too late.
我们走吧 趁现在还不太晚
...and let's draw a line in this direction.
...让我们在这个方向画一条线
I'm starving, I wish I can go right now.
我饿了 我希望我现在就能去
You should wait Odd, because there's still 3 hours left for dinner.....
你要等一下 Odd 因为还有3个小时才到晚餐.....
Odd and Ulrich, what are you two talking?
Odd和Ulrich 你们两个在说什么？
Oh, nothing, Ms. Hertz. Sorry.
哦 没什么 Hertz老师 对不起
All right, then. I don't want to hear anything.
好吧 那么 接下来我不想听到其他声音
I think you're not hungry anymore.
我想你已经不饿了
Okay, let's continue.
好了 我们继续吧
Hey, Einstein, have you finished the program?
嘿 爱因斯坦 你的程序完成了吗？
Almost finished.
差不多完成了
Franzs Hopper and I still have a lot of codes to crack that will take some time, if you ask me.
Franzs Hopper和我还有很多密码需要破解 还需要一些时间
I'm sure my father and you will finish it soon.
我相信我父亲和你很快就会完成它
What did I just say?
我刚才说什么了？
Oh, no. What was that?
哦 不 那是什么？
Guys, we should go to the factory. I have a bad feeling about this.
伙计们 我们应该去工厂了 我有一种不好的感觉
Ms. Hertz, we should evacuate the school.
Hertz老师 我们应该疏散学校
Yes, you're right, Jeremy. We should go somewhere safe right now.
是的 你说得对 Jeremy 我们现在应该去一个安全的地方
Do you think it's XANA?
你觉得是XANA在作怪吗？
Yes, I'm pretty sure. Look!
是的 我很确定 快看
Okay, let's go!
好了 我们走吧
Oh no, Einstein, they're everywhere!
情况不妙 爱因斯坦 他们到处都有
We're surrounded.
我们被包围了
Let's go this way, hurry!
我们往这边走 快点
Hello, father! XANA is attacking. XANA's sent monsters to the school!
喂？ 父亲 XANA发起进攻了 XANA派了怪物到学校
Oh no, this is an emergency. Come to the factory right now.
糟糕 情况紧急 马上到工厂来
You are going to Earth when you come here.
你来了之后就会去地球
Ok father, we are coming. This is getting serious.
好的 父亲 我们来了 这事越来越严重了
Welcome Lyoko warriors, what's the problem?
欢迎Lyoko战士们 有什么问题吗？
Our friend XANA has sent some monsters to the earth
我们的朋友XANA已经把一些怪物送到了地球上
just like he has done before.
就像他以前做的那样
XANA has sent some monsters to the school?
XANA把一些怪物送到了学校？
Then XANA can send some monsters to the factory too.
那么XANA也可以派一些怪物去工厂
What should we do? Protect the factory or protect the school?
我们怎么办？保护工厂还是保护学校？
You will have to split up, Odd and Aelita, Ulrich and Yumi.
你们必须分头行动 Odd和Aelita一起, Ulrich和Yumi一起
Ulrich and I will go and protect the school.
Ulrich和我去保护学校
Aelita and I will protect the factory.
Aelita和我将保护工厂
Great plan!
伟大的计划!
After you finish at the school, then return to here
在你们完成学校的任务后 再回到这里来
because I'm sure XANA will attack the factory with all its power!
因为我认为XANA会用它所有的力量来攻击工厂!
You guys must protect the factory because if XANA destroys it, it's game over!
你们必须全力保护工厂 因为如果XANA摧毁了它 游戏就结束了!
Jeremy is right. OK, go to the scanner room now.
Jeremy说得对 好了 现在去扫描室
Ok, let's do this.
好的 我们走吧
Transfer, Yumi.
传送 Yumi
Transfer, Aelita.
传送 Aelita
Transfer, Ulrich.
传送 Ulrich
Transfer, Odd.
传送 Odd
Scanner and virtualization.
扫描  虚拟化
Ok let's go to the Skid.
好了 我们去skid
Ok here we go.
好 我们走吧
Let's go.
出发吧
Ulrich and I can handle this. You two can go.
Ulrich和我可以处理这个 你们两个去忙吧
Ok. Father, vehicles!
好的 父亲 给我传送交通工具
Einstein, I want my Overboard so bad!
爱因斯坦 我非常需要我的滑板
Yes, it's my turn!
好啊 轮到我了
Let's go to the factory, Princess.
我们去工厂吧 公主
Jeremy, we're coming to the factory.
Jeremy 我们要去工厂了
Hurry up, Aelita, we can hear the monsters from here.
快点 Aelita 我从这里听到了怪物的声音
Ok yumi, let's do this.
好了Yumi 我们开始吧
They are coming.
他们来了
OK.
好的
Ok let's do this.
好了 我们开始吧
Jeremy, we're at the bridge and we're not alone.
Jeremy 我们在桥上 有人迎接我们
Aelita be careful.
Aelita要小心
Laser arrows!
激光箭
Nice shot, Odd!
射得好 Odd
Thanks, Einstein!
谢谢 爱因斯坦
And it's just the start.
而这只是个开始
Hey hey hey hey, this is too much!
嘿嘿嘿嘿 这太过分了
Are you okay Yumi?
你还好吗 Yumi？
Yes, but I'm tired.
还好 但我很累
I'm tired too but let's destroy all of them.
我也很累 但还是先把他们都消灭掉吧
Super-sprint!
超级冲刺
We're surrounded, Jeremy!
我们被包围了 Jeremy
We can't do anything.
我们现在什么都做不了
Where are Ulrich and Yumi?
Ulrich和Yumi在哪里？
They're still fighting.
他们还在战斗
Hurry up buddy, we need help!
快点 伙计 我们需要帮助
I'm sure they'll be here soon.
我相信他们很快就会来的
They're getting closer, let's go to the laboratory, Odd.
他们越来越接近了 我们去实验室吧 Odd
First, let's made them slower.
首先 我们要让他们慢一点
Laser arrows!
激光箭
Energy field!
能量球
Okay, Odd, run to the elevator.
好的 Odd 跑到电梯那里去
Dad, this is a disaster.
爸爸 这真是个灾难
They're everywhere.
敌人太多了
Oh no, we have to do something. We have to stop this madness.
哦 不 我们必须采取措施 必须阻止这种疯狂的行为
You and Jeremy could leave here.
你和Jeremy先离开这里吧
This is impossible sweet heart. If we leave here, no one can stop XANA.
这是不可能的 亲爱的 如果我们离开这里 就没有人可以阻止XANA了
This is our only chance.
这是我们唯一的机会
Wait a second, is that?
等一下 那是什么？
That's right Princess, they're here.
是的 公主 他们闯进来了